type Data = {
  question: String;
  optionA: String;
  optionB: String;
  optionC: String;
  optionD: String;
  correctOption: String;
};

const quizData: Array<Data> = [
  {
    question: "What is the deepest ocean in world",
    optionA: "Indian Ocean",
    optionB: "Pacific",
    optionC: "Antartica Ocean",
    optionD: "Bay of Bengal",
    correctOption: "optionB",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the 72nd element in periodic table",
    optionA: "Hafnium",
    optionB: "Helium",
    optionC: "Boron",
    optionD: "Lithium",
    correctOption: "optionA",
  },
  {
    question: "When was C# coding language created first",
    optionA: "2003",
    optionB: "2001",
    optionC: "2002",
    optionD: "2006",
    correctOption: "optionC",
  },
  {
    question: "When did the democracy started",
    optionA: "519 B.C",
    optionB: "508 B.C",
    optionC: "507 A.D",
    optionD: "507 B.C",
    correctOption: "optionD",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the smallest country in the world",
    optionA: "Vatican City",
    optionB: "Sri Lanka",
    optionC: "Maldives",
    optionD: "Italy",
    correctOption: "optionA",
  },
  {
    question: "Who invented Electricy",
    optionA: "William Gilbert",
    optionB: "Tesla",
    optionC: "Albert Eistein",
    optionD: "Boom Boo Taran",
    correctOption: "optionA",
  },
  {
    question: "Who actually invented Electricy and didnt got name",
    optionA: "William Gilbert",
    optionB: "Tesla",
    optionC: "Albert Eistein",
    optionD: "Boom Boo Taran",
    correctOption: "optionB",
  },
  {
    question: "How much ruppees is 27 USD if 1 USD is 75 Rs. for say",
    optionA: "75",
    optionB: "1015",
    optionC: "905",
    optionD: "2025",
    correctOption: "optionD",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the oldest IPhone üì±",
    optionA: "Iphone",
    optionB: "Iphone 5c",
    optionC: "Iphone 3GS",
    optionD: "Iphone 9 pro",
    correctOption: "optionA",
  },
  {
    question: "Where is the Taj Mahal located üè∑Ô∏è",
    optionA: "Conneticut",
    optionB: "Chennai",
    optionC: "New Delhi",
    optionD: "Agra",
    correctOption: "optionD",
  },
  {
    question: "What does UFO stands for",
    optionA: "Unidentified Fool in Office",
    optionB: "United Friends Office",
    optionC: "Un Identified Flying Object",
    optionD: "United Force of Omboliya",
    correctOption: "optionC",
  },
  {
    question: "What is newest coding language as of 2022",
    optionA: "VK#",
    optionB: "Rust",
    optionC: "Golang",
    optionD: "Julia",
    correctOption: "optionD",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you link CSS file to HTML",
    optionA: "<link>",
    optionB: "<script>",
    optionC: "<a>",
    optionD: "<div>",
    correctOption: "optionA",
  },
  {
    question: "How is the prime minister of India by 2022",
    optionA: "Rahul Gandi",
    optionB: "Narendra Modi",
    optionC: "Dan Androse",
    optionD: "Joe Biden",
    correctOption: "optionB",
  },
  {
    question: "If its 6PM in Australia, what's the time in India",
    optionA: "1:30 PM",
    optionB: "2:30 AM",
    optionC: "2:30 PM",
    optionD: "1:30 AM",
    correctOption: "optionA",
  },
  {
    question: "Which country has the most population",
    optionA: "Russia",
    optionB: "Pakistan",
    optionC: "China",
    optionD: "India",
    correctOption: "optionC",
  },
  {
    question: "When was 3x3 rubrics cube made",
    optionA: "1974",
    optionB: "1987",
    optionC: "1991",
    optionD: "1963",
    correctOption: "optionA",
  },
  {
    question: "When did India got Independence",
    optionA: "1958",
    optionB: "1956",
    optionC: "1959",
    optionD: "1957",
    correctOption: "optionD",
  },
  {
    question: "What does HTML stands for",
    optionA: "Hyper text markup language",
    optionB: "Hyper text markup languages",
    optionC: "hygro text markup language",
    optionD: "Hyper tube maarkup language",
    correctOption: "optionA",
  },
  {
    question: "Who made Go language",
    optionA: "Microsoft",
    optionB: "Google",
    optionC: "Amazon",
    optionD: "Facebook/ Meta",
    correctOption: "optionB",
  },
  {
    question: "Who made React frameword",
    optionA: "Microsoft",
    optionB: "Google",
    optionC: "Amazon",
    optionD: "Facebook/ Meta",
    correctOption: "optionD",
  },
  {
    question: "Who made Typescript",
    optionA: "Microsoft",
    optionB: "Google",
    optionC: "Amazon",
    optionD: "Facebook/ Meta",
    correctOption: "optionA",
  },
];

export default quizData;
